0h, it's-it's you again.
Okay, here's-here's what...
Here's what happened.
Carrie put on this brown wig
and was running out
into traffic,
and the guy I thought
was the bad guy isn't,
and her boyfriend
is the suicide bomber.
You believe that shit?
- Wrong show, frank.
- What?
That's homeland, not shameless.
Wow.
Don't mix Percocet with beer.
J'j' rock music j'j'
- who's the new barback?
- That's Santiago.
He's staying with us
until we find his father.
They were gonna go live
with his uncle in Indiana.
How are we gonna find
some random Guatemalan guy
in Gary, Indiana?
I did a web search:
"Where to find
illegal immigrants,
Gary, Indiana."
Got a whole list of places.
You find Santiago's uncle?
Oh, yeah. Found him
and then lost him.
Fly, my Mexican friend!
- Guatemalan.
- Guatemalan friend!
Fly!
Liam, your share
of the bills this month: $70.
- I'm nine.
- Figure it out.
Carl, your share of the bill
this month is 70 bucks.
Maybe you should get a real job
and stop hanging out
with your girlfriend so much.
Ingrid and I are pregnant.
- Triplets?
- Sextuplets.
And we're hiding
from a North Korean
fertility specialist,
so make room.
We are moving in.
Oh, that's hysterical.
Do you really think
we can afford more than one?
You'll get a job.
"Dreams dead? You're our man.
Be the hobo loco man."
Kev, what is this?
They're holding a competition
to choose the hobo loco
spokesperson.
The winner gets
a $50,000 contract
to be in a social media
campaign.
This is me.
I'm the hobo loco man.
You smell like a barroom floor.
I don't need anything from you!
She do this a lot?
Yeah.
Well, ia tely.
J'j' rock music j'j'
j'j' think of all
the luck you got j'j'
j'j' know that
it's not for naught j'j'
n you were beaming
once before if
j'j' but it's not like that
anymore j'j'
j'j' what is this downside j'j'
j'j' that you speak of? N
j'j' what is this feeling j'j'
j'j' you're so sure of? N
J'j' round up
the friends you got j'j'
j'j' know that
they're not for naught j'j'
n you were willing
once before if
j'j' but it's not like that
anymore j'j'
j'j' what is this downside j'j'
j'j' that you speak of? N
j'j' what is this feeling j'j'
j'j' you're so sure of? N
J'j' rock music j'j'
J'j' silicone sour j'j'
j'j' burning the hours
of the night away j'j'
n in retro bass j'j'
ii from the east side
moving right away j'j'
j'j' you're a satellite j'j'
J'j' and I'm on your website if
j'j' Miley doesn't miss you if
j'j' she got the spread
on the college issue j'j'
j'j' you're gonna try
to save her if
n you start to blame her... j'j'
oh, shit.
You open?
J'j' so you gotta be famous j'j'
twenty-four hours.
Ii it's a golden age j'j'
you sit wherever you want.
ii it's a golden age j'j'
I'll bring menus to you.
Are you hiring?
Ii it's a golden age j'j'
I'm a hard worker.
How about this booth
right over here?
Got any more
where this came from?
Couple hours after last call,
but get you some coffee.
So you're just drinking
on the job, then?
Everything okay out here, Fiona?
Let's get out of here.
Shit.
Shit. Shit.
You all right?
Good.
J'j' rock music j'j'
Nothing butjunk mail.
Rat shit in the attic.
Fires in the dryer vent.
These ads are terrifying.
Carbon monoxide leaks
from the furnace?
Fiona always handled this shit.
Should I be worried
about these things?
Ah, homeowner stuff.
Sucks to be an adult.
What? I'm eating for seven now.
Well, then all seven of you
are gonna need
to cough up cash
if you're gonna be living here.
All right.
I'm gonna do
some therapy sessions
on the phone this afternoon.
I'll write you a check later.
Hey. Where you guys going?
Softball camp.
I got a call from one of those
20 jobs I applied for.
Nice. Which one?
Some seafood restaurant place.
Carl Gallagher's going legit.
Minimum wage?
Only job someone like me
can get.
You know, you really
can't put "drug dealer"
or "gunrunner"
on your west point app.
Come on, babe.
Can we call the plumber guy?
Says he can snake our tub
for ten bucks.
What's wrong with our tub?
It has two inches
of scummy water in it
all the time that doesn't drain.
Good morning, family one.
Family two.
Why do you look
like a farm animal?
Smell like one too.
Your father is gonna be
the new hobo loco
beverage spokesperson.
Now, I haven't won
the competition yet, ingy.
Hobo what-o?
It's a delicious
alcoholic beverage.
They're looking for someone
with no purpose in life.
I finally found my calling.
Soon I'll be able
to support those I love.
Oh, yeah.
Wish me luck.
Oh, you go get 'em,
my hobo loco tiger.
Good-bye, little frank-ettes.
No need to even hold
a competition.
If it involves alcohol,
they should just
give him the prize.
Think we need to worry
about termites?
The hell's going on?
Jesus, it's almost 7:30.
Place is closed.
W-Well, where's Fiona?
We already turned away
a bunch of customers.
Well, let's get set up fast
so we don't lose
any more business.
Okay, let's get
the coffee going.
Fire up the grills.
Make sure the ketchups
are married.
I'll get the blinds.
All right, set the tables.
Let's go, guys. Come on.
Hey, Eliza.
She alive?
Yo, wakey-wakey!
- Get the fuck away from me!
- Whoa, whoa!
Take it easy!
Shit.
Sorry.
You okay?
Yeah. Uh, what time is it?
Why was this place locked?
Oh, uh...
I was doing the cash out late,
and I, uh, went
into the back office
for a second, and these...
Three sketchy guys
just came out of nowhere,
and I thought they were
gonna Rob me
or... I don't know what.
My god. Are you okay?
I-I locked up. I didn't know
if they were still
hanging around,
and I didn't want to go home
or take the I that late
in case they tried to follow me.
You left the cash out when
you went in the back office?
Yeah, it's fine.
All right.
Um, I'm gonna go
and take a shower,
and, uh, I will be back
for the lunch shift,
and it won't happen again.
See? Shampoo.
Not dish liquid.
That's an interesting concept.
Here, let me show you.
All right.
Oh, man. Yeah, that, uh...
That actually feels really good.
I give great head, huh?
Yeah, it's better
than your regular head.
- Hey!
- Knock, knock, knock!
- Just me.
- Jesus, dude!
And I'm not looking
at your dick.
I just left my retainer in here.
I lied.
I looked at your dick. Bye!
Hey, your stupid boyfriend
still owes me $300
for the comcast bill!
You gotta lose those guys.
Yeah, then I gotta go
through the bullshit
of getting a new roommate.
Okay, turn around. Your turn.
- All right.
- Are you off today?
Me too.
We should do something.
Why? You're not
hanging around with Boone?
No, he's on his way
back to Yemen.
Isn't that where
all those land mines are?
Fingers crossed.
So let's hang out.
Never done that before.
We could see if we even
like each other.
I got boring shit to do all day.
Me too. We can do it together.
Aah! Turn around.
- Take a look.
- Oh, nice.
- It's good.
- Yeah, I like it.
Right, you see,
I give good head too.
What is this?
Diablas! Las diablas!
Sanfiago.
He probably had
a nightmare again.
- Ow!
- Die! Die!
Girls! Whoa, whoa, whoa.
- Stop. What are you doing?
- Hey! You're hurting him!
- You duct taped him?
- And handcuffs?
Santiago, I am so sorry.
You have to forgive them.
The-the girls
are a little bit wild.
Preschool was supposed
to be taming them.
Come on, baby.
Let's go get you some juice.
Girls, what has gotten into you?
- We don't hurt people.
- We don't?
No, of course not.
We have to be nice,
and Santiago's
part of our family.
- No.
- Yes, honey,
and his sister's
gonna be here soon too.
No, they go home.
They don't have a home.
Bad people wanted
to turn them into sex slaves
and gang members.
Kev, please stop talking.
I'm trying to teach them. I'm...
They're four years old.
Come on, girls.
It's time to get dressed
for school.
Take Santiago to the bar.
Santiago.
What do you say?
Me and you having some
quality dad time together?
Huh? Let's do it!
No, no.
God, I'm so sorry.
Yeah, just hold up the shirt.
Nice!
Hey, hobo loco is trending
in the top 50 right now.
Thought we'd have, like,
30 homeless here
and that'd be it.
Hey, everyone!
Let me all hear you say,
"I love hobo loco!"
I love hobo loco!
Are you fucking kidding me?
Who are all these people?
Jesus.
Hey, is everybody here
for the hobo loco competition?
Apparently so,
but I'm gonna win this thing.
Gonna be hard,
since I'm a shoo-in.
That right?
I've never held the same job
for more than 37 days.
I spent my life savings
on a blockbuster franchise
in 2013.
I buried a bipolar wife,
a cancer-riddled girlfriend,
and a mother who never loved me.
Two-thirds of my penis
got blown off
in the first Gulf war.
I won the lottery in 2006
and accidentally used
the winning ticket
as a rolling paper.
I grew up in flint, Michigan.
Frank Gallagher.
Mikey o'shea.
Irish, huh?
Well, the dead junkie
whose wallet I acquired was.
Very impressive.
Why do these fucking posers
think they can steal
our thunder?
Because their parents told them
they could be anything
they wanted to be.
Let's teach 'em a lesson.
Let's kick ass.
Excuse us. Excuse us.
- Excuse me!
- Excuse us.
- Vip!
- Coming through.
Coming through. This way.
One second.
Look out. Oh, hey,
hey, hey, hey, hey.
Let the real hobos through!
Don't be rude. Don't be rude.
- Hey, hey, hey, hey!
- Come on, excuse us.
- Hey! Hey, hey, hey.
- Good god.
We're here for the competition.
- Where do we sign?
- They cut the line!
And that's exactly
the kind of spunk
we're looking for.
Do you hear that,
phi piggie piggie?
That's what they're looking for.
Get your spunk-less ass
out of here!
- You should learn.
- Hey, fellas.
I just... I just need you
to sign in right here.
Oh, right away.
- Done.
- Again, yeah.
Great. Mm-hmm.
Okay, next,
I'm gonna need to test
your baseline
blood alcohol content.
Right this way.
Here we are.
J'j' rock music j'j'
Point two-three.
Nice.
Point two-seven.
Whoa.
All in a day's work.
Whoo. Great job.
Okay, now, over here,
you're gonna need
to drink two ounces
of hobo loco
in less than 15 seconds,
and please,
no throwing up on me.
Please use the trash can
over here.
Okay, and...
OMG. That was amazing.
It's like drinking water.
More like watered-down water.
Well, have a hobo loco hat.
Agency will be announcing
the contestants
in just a bit.
All right, next.
Good luck, j-holes.
You hear that, douchebags?
This is the dining area.
I was really impressed
with your résumé.
- Really?
- Kitchen.
Military man, hmm?
Mmm-mmm.
Um, okay.
And this is the employee lounge.
Your uniform: Right in here.
Let me know if you need
any help putting it on.
Hey, so what's the job?
Busboy, uh, dishwasher?
Street corner sign spinner.
J'j' hip-hop music if
m we iookin' fresh when
we steppin' in the vip j'j'
- j'j' look at us, look at us j'j'
- j'j' everybody gonna notice we j'j'
j'j' dressed so fly
like an f-16 j'j'
j'j' they stare with they mouth
wide open, uh j'j'
j'j' close your mouth
and let me buy your drinks j'j'
j'j' while I kick it
with this chick in pink j'j'
j'j' she compliment me
on my cufflinks j'j'
n I compliment her
on some other things if
j'j' okay, where all my fresh,
fly people on the east side? J'j'
j'j' where all my fresh, fly
people on the West Side? J'j'
people on the south side? J'j'
n north side, any side? J'j'
j'j' I'm so fly, yo,
they call me aviator j'j'
j'j' plush with the finish
on my swag out the hangar j'j'
j'j' known for the hot 163
and the bangers j'j'
j'j' think I'm 'bout to take
that three-piece j'j'
j'j' off the hanger... j'j'
hey, franny.
What is that?
Careful. Here.
Hey.
What's going on in here?
Morning sickness.
Snaking the tub.
I got it.
That's disgusting!
- Damn.
- Oh.
I should add "plumber"
to my welding résumé.
All right, may I take
a shower, please?
Hey, do you ever do those things
in the saver special?
Check for carbon monoxide leaks
or clean the dryer vent?
No. Too busy, you know,
raising five kids and frank.
Well, make it quick in there.
Make sure you clean up
your hair in the drain after.
Yeah, all right.
J'j' rock music j'j'
sorry I snapped at you.
You're doing a good job.
Thanks.
Also, I'm working
the lunch shift later,
so I'll have money
for you today.
Good.
Really helps
my morning sickness.
80 should we, like,
hold hands or something?
I don't know.
Your hands get all sweaty?
They will now
that you asked me like that.
Are you a top or bottom?
- Bottom.
- Ah, see, me too.
This will never work.
It's all right.
We're here anyway.
A nursing home?
Yeah.
I volunteer here once a month.
Come on, you can help me.
Shit.
Hey, are we gonna
be cleaning bedpans or...
What up, bitches?
Tami, Audrey got
denture cream in my hair.
Aww, let me see that.
I did not do that.
Tomorrow you'll say
you did do it.
Make up your Alzheimer's-y mind.
All right, ladies.
Who's at the bowls first?
I've got an assistant today,
so we can do two at a time.
- Me too.
- What are we doing?
- Washing their hair.
We're washing their hair?
Yeah. Watch out for that one.
She's handsy,
likes to grab a dick.
Hey. You all set?
J'j' upbeat music if
j'j' whoo j'j'
ii“ I died when I was born j'j'
j'j' I'm living
through this nuclear age j'j'
n this money's
running dry... j'j'
hey.
Hey. What's up, man?
What are you doing?
Giving Santiago
more of an American look
before we go to the alibi.
J'j' let's get that paper j'j'
j'j' you're losing
and I'm winning j'j'
j'j' but who's keeping score... j'j'
J'j' let's get that paper j'j'
You're getting his sister too?
Yeah. Foster people are gonna be
dropping her off
a little bit later.
There you go.
And the final touch.
Huh?
Oh. Okay.
How's he look?
Like a cheesy American.
Nice.
So you got a lady friend
back home?
Mm, sure do.
Jasmine dawn.
Except she kicked me out
three years ago.
Strapping young man like you?
Yeah, well, I had
too many blackouts
for her to deal with.
But I become the hobo loco man,
though,
she gotta take me back, right?
As long as she'll settle
for runner-up.
Won't have to.
You got loser
written all over you.
All right, good afternoon!
Yes, welcome.
Thank you for entering
our hobo loco man search...
Or hobo loco woman,
of course. Yes, ladies.
All right, we have reviewed
your applications,
and we're ready to announce
the 20 contestants.
If your name is called,
please come on up
to the hobo loco porch.
Bethany houseman!
- There's Bethany!
- Hey, all right.
Next up, Victor...
"Nag-high."
- Victor! My man.
- Yay!
- All right.
- Next up:
Frank Gallagher!
Whoo! Yes! Where is he?
- Hey, there he is.
- That's frank.
There he is!
All right. Gloria sweetland.
Oh, she's got fans.
Uh-oh.
Mikey o'shea!
- Mikey, Mikey, Mikey.
- Yeah.
We got a competition now.
- Hola.
Next up, Mrs. O'coin.
Right. There she is.
Oh, hey. Hey, hey, hey, hey.
No means no, Audrey, all right?
There you go.
So what boring stuff are you
gonna have me do with you today?
Uh, gotta buy
a new phone charger,
some socks,
then go grocery shopping.
Debs has us on rotation.
It's my turn.
I can help you get
some healthy stuff.
Do you know they actually have
produce aisles
at the grocery store?
Hmm, you don't say.
This feels so good.
It's been a long time
since a boy's
run his fingers through my hair.
Hey, uh, how long
you been volunteering here?
Uh, since beauty school.
My grandma Peggy
used to live here.
Hmm? What'd you say?
I wasn't talking to you,
broom hilda.
I was telling lip
about my grandma Peggy.
The whore?
She fucked your boyfriend
one time. Get over it.
You know, that shit shouldn't
matter once you're past 75.
I will never forget.
Okay, well, that's good.
You hold on to that.
Mm-hmm. Mm-hmm.
You're smiling at me
in that way.
What way?
That you like me.
Well, it's kind of hard not to
when you're
putting rollers
in some lady's hair
on your day off.
- Oh, whoa.
- Audrey, stop.
- Whoa, whoa, whoa.
- Leave him alone.
That's my dick.
'Sup, small fry?
Saw the sign in the window.
"Help wanted." I need a job.
How old are you?
Twenty-five.
Yeah, come back when you're 31.
Okay.
What do you do with those
squeezed-out lemons?
Whool
Okay, congratulations, hobos.
For the next week,
you'll be sleeping
in this backyard
and be required to drink
16 ounces of hobo loco daily.
Each day, you'll be given
timed challenges.
Those of you who fail
to complete the tasks
will be eliminated.
You'll also need
to create brand awareness.
You each get a phone
and two quarts of hobo loco.
Take lots of photos and videos
of folks sampling
your hobo loco.
All right, who's ready
for the first challenge?
- Yeah!
- Yay.
In the spirit of a true hobo,
each contestant will forage
for their own bedding
to sleep on tonight.
You will be judged
on creativity
and resourcefulness.
You have one hour.
All right, let's go out there,
start hobo-ing!
Okay!
- Frank!
- What are you doing?
- Come on, frank!
- Get off of me. No!
Wait for me!
Argh, Matey.
Popcorn shrimp is back.
J'j' rock music j'j'
fucking sh...
Aye, aye, Matey.
Popcorn shrimp is back.
Hey, butt pirate,
need a soda with your shrimp?
Fuck you, douchebag!
Aye, aye, Matey.
Popcorn shrimp. Fuck.
When did we plant grass in here?
- That's mold.
- Ah, fuck.
When'd you guys
suddenly get into cleaning?
Makes Santiago happy.
Yeah, we're doing stuff
he likes.
Hey, uh, Santiago said
your girls are trying
to murder him.
Is that what they were doing
this morning?
Wait, that's what they
were doing this morning?
He called them ias diablas...
The devils.
But he's okay with it,
because he doesn't want you
to send him back.
We're not gonna send him back.
Why would the girls
want to murder him?
They're not trying
to murder anyone.
- They're just playing.
- Maybe they're jealous...
Sibling rivalry.
Maybe they're
just not into having
some random brown dude
who doesn't speak English
living in their house.
They're brown too.
Different shade of brown.
Oh, that's crazy.
Just as crazy as white people,
who are actually pink,
thinking all black people
are the same color.
Well, what about
brownish white people,
like some Italians
or Portuguese or Spanish?
They can be
as brown as Santiago.
They're European brown.
All right, I'm lost.
What are you talking about?
Okay, it's real simple.
Your girls
are a different brown
than Santiago,
so they want his different brown
to go home where he belongs
and leave their brown to get
all the good stuff from america.
Are you saying our girls
are racist?
He's saying Amy and Gemma
don't understand
what's going on.
What if they want
to murder martina
when she shows up?
No one's murdering anyone.
- Who's martina?
- Santiago's sister.
If she's the same color brown
as him,
they're gonna want
to murder her.
Oh, shut up, Tommy.
It'd like Kermit said.
They're just jealous.
We're gonna talk to them
after school
and tell them there's plenty
of good stuff in america
for all the brown people
so they don't have
to end up in jail
for murdering
the different brown people
or something like that, right?
Hey, I recognize you.
You're that crazy lady's
ex-husband.
- Yeah. Is she here?
- Gallaghers don't snitch.
I got a phone app
that says she's in there.
Oh, okay.
Make yourself useful
and get the door.
All right.
There you go.
Cool if I look around?
Knock yourself out.
Might be upstairs.
- Ingrid?
- You fall?
- No.
- Ingrid!
Just making sure
my embryos stay in.
Where are you?
I'm selling lemonade
to make money
so I can sleep indoors again.
Ingrid?
What the hell are you doing?
Vacuuming the lint
out of the dryer vents
before they catch on fire.
Ingrid, where...
Ingrid.
Ingy.
What are you doing here?
Dr. Kwan called me.
She told me you were pregnant.
That's wonderful.
Wonderful?
You never wanted me
to have children
because of my condition.
Well, now that you are pregnant,
it's a beautiful miracle.
Let's do this together.
They're not even yours.
They're frank's.
Yes, but you just met him.
You think he's really committed
to having more kids?
Yes. Yes.
But I'm the one who's always
been there for you,
and I always will,
so let's get you
back on your meds
and then we'll go
for a checkup with Dr. Kwan.
You're trying to trick me.
You're gonna get me
on that exam table
and then have kwan just suck
the embryos out of me!
No, I won't. I won't, I promise.
We'll keep two.
We'll have twins.
Wouldn't that be great? Twins?
Bullshit.
You don't want my babies.
Frank does. Frank loves me.
He loves all six of my embryos.
I have a phone patient now,
so please go.
Okay, okay.
I'll check back in later.
Hey, Debbie.
Randy's wrong.
Frank'll be committed
to my six babies, right?
Not a chance.
J'j' rock music j'j'
What are you on my ass for?
Find your own bedding.
This is my spot.
I thought we could make a pact.
Either one of us wins,
we split the spokesman money,
50/50.
You trying to hone in
on my dough?
Or am I trying to give you
half of mine, hmm?
You're a crafty dude, Mikey o.
I'm a lone wolf. Go.
Suit yourself.
- Suit yourself.
- Go!
J'j' hey, man, don't you ll”
j'j' don't you know j'j'
j'j' your mom don't care j'j'
j'j' hey, man... j'j'
jackpot
j'j' forget what I said n
Hey, yo! What are you
doing in that truck?
Get out of there!
- Hey!
- I-I'm, uh...
Get back here!
Where the fuck
do you think you're going?
That's what you get!
Serves you right, asshole!
Yeah, you better keep running!
So was it weird buying
actual green things
at the grocery store?
Hey, I've bought
green things before.
Guacamole, mountain dew,
jell-o,
mint chocolate chip ice cream.
You gonna list every
crappy green thing?
Yeah, I can go on.
Shamrock shakes.
Green eggs and ham.
Xan?
I didn't know where else to go.
Aye, Matey!
Popcorn shrimp is back.
Oh, my god. Check this out.
Gallagher?
Shit.
What's up, little shins?
What, you out here selling?
Just popcorn shrimp.
'Cause we took over this corner.
I don't like no competition.
Hey, you won't have any from me.
So how do I know this whole
gay pirate shit
ain't some front?
I've been out of the business
for years.
I'm just working
at captain Bob's now.
I got trust issues, man.
What can I say?
I'm gonna have to shake your
Johnny Depp-looking ass down,
make sure
you ain't got no stash.
Yo, I swear to you, I don't.
Shake him.
Fuck. They're just shrimp!
J'j' put 'em on the battlefields
where they're dead... j'j'
Come on, put me down,
motherfucker!
Watch the hat!
So what happened?
Xan, where's your mom?
Don't know.
Here.
I'll make you something to eat.
W-When's the last time
you saw her?
She went to get pizza.
I waited in the motel.
Watched TV and stuff.
What, and she never came back?
J'j' somber music if
here you go.
Motel guy kicked me out.
When did this happen?
Couple days ago.
Where have you been
since then, xan?
Sometimes my mom works
at this truck stop.
I just hung out there.
A truck stop?
There's a bunch
of guys there, but...
My mom never showed up.
Wait, wait, wait,
a bunch of guys?
W-What does that mean?
They fucking touch you?
- Chill out.
- No, I'm not gonna chill
the fuck out.
Her mother ditched her again!
Okay, well, you are scaring her.
I'll give her a bath.
I'll talk to her.
I'll find out
if anything happened.
Okay?
Okay.
It's okay.
I'm sorry, xan.
Lemonade!
Get your fresh lemonade!
Come get your lemonade.
Let me have one
for each one of my guys.
That'll be five bucks.
Keep the change.
Thanks.
How long are you guys
gonna be out here?
I don't know. A while.
J'j' I love who you are n
j'j' I love who you are n
you're blocking my driveway.
J'j' who you are n“
lemonade!
Get your fresh lemonade!
Jesus.
Want some lemonade?
Just a sprite.
Last night fucked with me.
Got a whole new attitude.
- Great.
- Ah, perfect.
Uh, Tina,
I got table 41's food for you.
Yeah, okay.
Grilled ham and cheese...
For you,
and the tacos must be for you.
- Enjoy.
- Yes. Thank you.
- Margo.
- Good afternoon.
What brings you here?
Police got a 911 call last night
about a possible robbery.
A frantic woman called,
saying that three men
were threatening her,
and she said they left
but she was afraid
they were gonna come back.
And when the police arrived,
the restaurant was closed,
which is interesting,
since we're open 24 hours.
Maybe they had
the wrong address.
Stop.
I don't want your lies,
and you smell like booze.
I don't know if you're drunk now
or if you just drank
so much last night
that it's just coming
out of your pores.
No, I'm sober.
You're fired.
Well, why?
I-I haven't had a drink
today, I swear.
I've been getting calls
for the past month,
from customers and vendors
and employees,
saying that you had been drunk
on the job
or asleep on the job
or angry on the job.
Please don't fire me. Please.
I-I've had
a rough couple months,
but-but I've turned a corner.
People who say
they've "turned a corner"...
They haven't turned a corner.
They're just trying
to convince everyone they have.
Please give me another chance.
I promise I'll straighten out.
Good.
- You should.
- Yes.
But not on my watch.
You're acting manager now,
so you make sure she cleans
her things up and leaves.
Fuck all of you.
Ratting me out.
If it weren't for me,
none of you na motherfuckers
would even have a job. Mm-hmm.
I wanted to fire you
because you suck,
but you called me, crying
about your mother
and her medical bills,
and I let you
keep your fucking job.
Fiona, I think we should just...
Shut the fuck up, Eliza.
I'm leaving.
Oh, and guess what?
The cook rubbed his dick
on all of your meals.
Yeah, enjoy.
Can I get the check, please?
Fuck this, Matey.
What happened to you?
I got beat up,
shoes thrown at me,
I don't even know how many
milkshakes and beers.
You poor baby.
Come here. Come here.
Um, yeah, I don't think
it's the best idea
to be spinning signs out there.
Got any otherjobs in here?
Are you kidding me?
I got a folder full
of applicants wanting jobs:
People with master's degrees,
anthropologists
and English majors
and useless things like that.
Wow. Oh, okay.
Besides, you did a great job
out there today.
Sales are up 20%.
I'm ordering more
popcorn shrimp as we speak.
So you'll be back tomorrow,
right?
Uh, yeah. Sure.
Sweetie pies, why were you
hitting Santiago this morning?
'Cause we don't like him.
Why? Santiago's a good guy.
He leaves now?
No, baby, he doesn't leave now.
He's staying here with us.
He's our family.
Oh, fuck.
Girls, is this
because Santiago's
a different shade of brown
than you?
Or, girls, is this because
you're jealous of Santiago?
We need to treat people
how we want to be treated.
There are people in this world
who want to send brown people
like us back to Africa,
but we won't stand for it,
will we?
No. So we also won't stand
for them wanting to send
other kinds of brown people
back to Central America.
Get it?
Let me try. Uh, snookums,
I used to have sibling rivalry
with the kids
in my foster homes, okay?
Especially this one boy,
Joey caccitore.
He used to kiss up
to my foster parents
all the time,
and they would give him
extra butterscotch pudding,
and I thought
that they loved him more,
but in reality,
they just hated all of us.
- Kev, how is that helping?
- I don't know.
I forget that's how
the story ended.
I'll get it.
Talk about
the brown people more.
I think that was helping.
Just because Santiago's here
doesn't mean we love you less,
and just because he's different
doesn't mean that
we're gonna get rid of him.
- V.
- Yeah?
- Look who it is.
- Hi.
Martina!
Santiago!
J'j' rock music j'j'
Only 30 seconds left.
What the hell was that?
Smacking me with
a two by four out there?
That's the way
we're gonna play this thing?
All's fair in love
and hobo wars, frank.
Gauntlet thrown, my friend.
Just got off the phone
with the client.
Four Greek councils
have signed deals
to make hobo loco their
featured alcoholic beverage
at all their fraternity parties.
- We're blowing up.
- Mm-hmm.
The insta' story I just posted
less than an hour ago
already has 100,000 views.
Oh, sorry, Victor.
You've been eliminated.
And then there were 19.
Cardboard amateur.
Bubble wrap.
Nice touch, frank.
Ooh, but not as clever
as insulation and tarp!
- Ha!
- You are the winner
- of this challenge, Mikey o.
- Yeah!
All right, let's get out there
for our next challenge:
Dumpster diving for your dinner.
Who thinks they can bring back
the best meal?
- I can!
- Well, let's see!
Whoo! Go! Go! Go!
- Whoo!
- One hour! Let's go!
Don't forget to share
your hobo loco
on social media!
We're gonna make
the American hobo
as famous as Joe camel.
You did good, coming here.
You know, lip's a smart guy.
Ilike him.
He'll figure this out.
But you can't be hanging out
at truck stops, right?
It's a lot of creepy people
out there.
Look, if I saw...
If I saw a little girl
on the street alone,
I would want to protect her,
make sure she was safe,
but there are
some bad people out there
who'd want to hurt her,
maybe say stuff
or do stuff to her.
If that ever happened,
you can tell me about it.
Hey, I'd listen to anything
you have to say,
try and make you feel better,
or maybe even beat the shit
out of that person.
I don't know.
Come on.
Let's go raid lip's closet
and find you
something clean to wear.
J'j' rock music j'j'
No, Sally, I didn't say
that you were responsible
for Lou not remembering
your birthday.
I said you were responsible
for the way you reacted
to Lou not remembering
your birthday.
Guess who just got
fucking fired!
Are you shushing me
in my own house?
She's doing
a phone therapy session
with her client Sally.
Oh. Hey, Sally.
Sally, I got all the therapy
you could ever need right here!
- Sorry, Sally...
- What happened?
Why'd you get fired?
Bullshit this, bullshit that,
blah, blah, blah.
So what's your plan now?
Gonna hang around here,
drinking all day?
Oh, no, I-I might
eat something too.
What about money?
Could you stop whining about
money for two seconds, maybe?
Brought some popcorn shrimp
back from my shitty-ass job.
- Yum.
- I'm turning the furnace on.
Gotta check
for carbon monoxide leaks.
You need a job, Fiona.
Mm-hmm.
What the hell?
No! Shit!
Come on.
Help!
I'm stuck down here!
I'm coming. I'm coming.
I said I'm coming!
So, uh, what I'm hearing
you say, Sally,
is that even though
you're still mad at Lou,
you are willing to focus
on the good things he does.
Sally, your therapist
is having a tea party
with stuffed animals.
Door's open.
We're looking for Ingrid.
I'm her ex-husband.
This is Dr. Kwan...
Oh, I don't give a fuck
who you are.
She's right here.
Yeah, you know, Sally,
we will have
to continue this later
same time next week.
I cannot believe
that you betrayed me
and brought her here.
Ingrid, Dr. Kwan explained to me
that you will bleed out and die
if you carry six babies to term.
Then why did you implant
all those embryos in me?
Because there was only
a five percent chance
of any of them
surviving implantation
in your shriveled-up uterus.
So what you're saying is,
I'm a medical miracle?
You'll be a medical tragedy
if you carry all six
of those fetuses to term.
I am willing to take my chances.
Ingrid, we are gonna go
to Dr. Kwan's office.
- No.
- She is gonna do
- the procedure, and then...
- No, no, no, no.
I will take you home.
No! Get out of my house!
Bitch, if you don't come
to my office right now,
I will go North Korean on you
and reach into your vagina
and rip those embryos
out of you with my bare hands!
Doctor, please!
She is trying to kill my babies!
Ingrid?
J'j' rock music j'j'
ingfid? Oh, crap.
Ingy.
Ingrid? Open this door!
- Please.
- Hello?
- Is somebody down here?
- Please!
- I'm trapped!
- Ingrid.
Well, we all feel trapped
at some point.
Uh, do you want
to talk about it?
No, you crazy bitch!
It's Debbie!
I need to get out of here
and turn off the gas
before the house blows up!
Help!
Somebody help!
Kelly?
My pants are stuck.
Can you take them off?
Just take off your pants!
Oh, my god.
J'j' energetic rock music I”!
Nice ass.
Let's get that gas turned off.
I!“ and I got what you need I!“
I!“ sing hallelujah,
I'll make you believe I"!
J'j' 'cause you do what I do
and I do me... j'j'
thank you for dinner,
fancy French restaurant.
Oh, yeah!
Any escargots in here?
I!“ here we go, here we go... j'j'
Whoa! Hey!
Come on! Hey!
All's fair, Mikey o. All's fair.
Come on, now!
Come on! Aww!
J'j' boredom, boredom,
boredom, boredom j'j'
j'j' boredom, boredom, boredom j'j'
j'j' boy my bedroom floor
is a cereal burial... j'j'
what's going on, fellas?
Nothing. Just selling lemonade.
Neighbor said
there was a disturbance.
Yeah, officer, I called.
That was me.
Seems to be the problem?
These kids are up to no good.
They are making
way too much noise, okay?
They are getting water
on my car.
Noise? That's Tyler the creator.
They don't belong here, sir.
We live two streets over.
Well, I mean,
do you have a-a permit
to operate a food stand
in front of my house?
Ask them, sir. Do they?
You need a permit
to sell lemonade?
Eighty-three-ten will respond.
Move the lemonade stand
down the street
and turn down the music.
Wait, sir, that's it?
What do you want me to do, lady?
Shut them down.
I just got my car washed.
You know what?
Looks like y'all made
enough money.
Why don't you close up shop
for the day?
What? Why?
Just do it.
It's not worth the aggravation.
Here's 20 bucks.
Get yourself a permit.
I!“ got some cars I can handle I!“
I!“ but nowhere
for performance... j'j'
well, you heard the man.
Shut the shit down.
I!“ but I hate eating solo j'j'
I!“ need someone we can
loiter in parking lots j'j'
I!“ and sunsets at the border,
yeah j'j'
j'j' ringy-dingy-dong,
I can't be alone j'j'
j'j' ibeen starting to feel... j'j'
This is great.
Big family dinner.
This is exactly what I wanted.
Are you enjoying
the food, martina?
Better than what they had
in the holding cell.
I am so sorry
they put you there.
This is not what america's
normally like.
I thought you were
supposed to be
the greatest country
in the world.
You caught us at a bad time.
Hey, what do you say we, um,
finish up dinner
and watch some TV? Hmm?
You guys have pawn stars
in Guatemala?
Uh, we cannot stay after dinner.
We have to go back.
Back? To the detention center?
To Guatemala.
We go tonight with our uncle.
Your uncle?
Jose Gomez?
Our father was deported,
so we have to go back
to be with him.
Deported? I'm so sorry.
Si. Thank you for
offering to foster us,
but your country no longer wants
the tired and poor,
yearning to be free,
like the big green lady
in the New York harbor says.
Big green lady?
Statue of Liberty.
She's been napping a long time.
Probably hasn't slept in days.
Yeah, you know,
you can go if you want.
Are you giving me permission?
No, I just mean
if this is too much
to deal with,
you know, I understand.
You really think I do
anything I don't want to do?
No, probably not.
Damn right.
Got you. Yes.
Hey, buddy. What's up?
Some lady called the cops on me.
What'd you do?
Nothing, just selling lemonade
in front of her house.
Said we got water
on her fancy car.
What lady?
Over on Bundy.
The one who bought
Mr. Reeback's house
and redid it?
Who were you with?
Some friends from school,
Todd and de-Shawn.
Black kids?
Motherfucker.
We're not gonna eat
this stuff, right?
Oh, no, hell no.
We're gonna fear factor
this shit.
I made it!
I made it.
Shit. Damn it.
Can't keep this player
from the game, frank.
How did you get out?
Garbage truck came by.
Dumped me in the back.
It was rough,
but a pile of old big macs
broke my fall.
All right, welcome back.
We'll now go around
and take our pick
for the dumpster dive
competition.
Sushi, huh?
Brave choice.
J'j' rock music I”!
You know that new bitch
over on Bundy?
Yeah, she pulled
some racist shit
on my brother Liam,
so block party. Come on.
J'j' hit 'em where it hurts j'j'
I!“ get out now
and leave me in the dirt... j'j'
hey, Mr. Jackson. We're throwing
a new racist neighbor
a welcome party.
Bring your pit bull.
Come on, boy. Let's go.
I!“ I'm making a comeback j'j'
I!“ you gotta believe that n
I!“ oh, yeah I"!
Welcome to the south side,
bitch!
I!“ I'm making a comeback j'j'
you sure you want to do this?
Si.
I have no idea what he said.
It was good. He smiled.
There goes my son.
I have called the police.
They are on their way.
You are disturbing the peace.
Hey, lady.
That was my brother
with the lemonade stand.
- What?
- That's right.
I got a black brother.
What?
That's why you didn't want him
near your house, right?
'Cause he's black?
Okay, you need to go home.
Some of us have jobs.
You know, I lived
in this neighborhood
my whole life.
Kids have always
sold lemonade right here.
Black kids, white kids,
Russian kids, Mexican kids.
Would you get away
from my fence?
Nobody ever had a problem
with lemonade stands
until all of you bougie,
yoga-loving,
latte-sipping,
ankle tattoo-wearing,
racist assholes
moved into our neighborhood,
so your fence?
Fuck your fence.
Ah, shit!
Hey!
J'j' rock music I”!
J'j' well, I'm about to explode j'j'
I!“ let it out, let it go j'j'
I!“ and if you're down
for the show I!”
J“! I got something
I've been keeping secret j'j'
j'j' shown never before I!
J'j' 'bout to kick in the door j'j'
j'j' I know you want it
some more I!“
I!“ but I've got no time left
for tongue in cheek and n”
j'j' I've got, got, got
to let it out I”!
J'j' ooh, ooh, ooh, ooh j'j'
j'j' I've got, got, got to n“
video of the food challenge
went viral.
Over 400,000 views.
People are doing something
called the "hobo dragon."
We are totally getting
promoted after this.
Another
alcohol poisoning inside?
Yeah, fourth one today.
J'j' I've got, got, got
to let it out I”!
I!“ let it out, let it out,
let it out I!"
- J'j' ooh, ooh j'j'
- j'j' oh, oh, oh I!”
- J'j' oh, oh, oh I!”
- J'j' ooh, ooh j'j'
- j'j' oh, oh, oh I!”
I!“ let it out, let it out,
let it out I!"
- J'j' ooh, ooh j'j'
- j'j' oh, oh, oh I!”
- J'j' oh, oh, oh I!”
- J'j' ooh, ooh j'j'
- j'j' oh, oh, oh I!”
I!“ let it out, let it out,
let it out I!"